[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Angie, can you hear me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "But do you know which one it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WDT", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, (speaking in foreign language).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Did she say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "And do you know if there were any other children in the house that these women were being kept?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Well, no, because we never -- well, I never saw these girls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Did you know what he did for a living?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "He's like a 50-year-old man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Did you speak to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "When Amanda Berry ran into your aunt's house, did she say anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "She just say the phone.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Berry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And then she used the phone herself to call the police, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "And how long did it take the police to get to your house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, that was quick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "So a few minutes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I don't think not even -- a minute, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "And what happened then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, the thing is that they didn't believe at first.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Did your aunt see the other women being brought out of the house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "And what kind of condition was Amanda Berry in, did your aunt say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Really bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Berry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "RB", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Your aunt is crying or Amanda Berry was crying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "No, my aunt is crying because she said she couldn't believe so many years living here and never notice nothing suspicious.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Berry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "But we didn't know much about Michelle Knight but the other two girls had been the subject of many vigils by their families, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Knight"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "And did your aunt see the other women coming out of the property after the police arrived?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, she said the last one that came out of the house, it was a girl, she might have been like 10 years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "And has your aunt now given a statement to the police?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "This is a really extraordinary story, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "It really is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "How does it make you feel, having been through something like this as a parent, when you hear about something like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I'm overjoyed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "And given all your experience in these kind of cases, what would be the most pressing and urgent things that these young women as they are now will have to go through in terms of readapting back to normal life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, I don't have a lot of experience in the reunification process, but I can assure you they'll need to be tested medically, they will need to undergo I would imagine some intense psychological counseling for a very long period of time, because they will have a lot of different conflicting thoughts going through their minds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "John, this is really quite extraordinary, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Piers, it's incredible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, John said it many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What can you tell me about the latest on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, what I can tell you is that it's almost like a carnival atmosphere on the street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "But was the general feeling that they must be dead, that it had been so long with no real leads, that was the only conclusion people could reach?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "You need police, fire or ambulance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I need police.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What's going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "I've been kidnapped and I've been with him for ten years and I'm here, I'm free now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What's your address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I can't hear you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Hello?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Are they on their way right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: As soon as we get a car open.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Who's the guy you're -- who's the guy who went out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "His name is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "How old is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "He's like 52.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Is he white, black or Hispanic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "He's Hispanic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "What's he wearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I don't know, because he's not here right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Who knows?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "The police are on the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Talk to them when they get there, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "And Sylvia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I was in a business meeting and I got a 911 text call, my cousin.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sylvia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Do you know, Sheila, the reaction of Gina's mother when she heard the news?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I do not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sheila", "Gina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Sylvia, did the family ever give up hope that one day Gina would be found alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VB", "RP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "They never did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "It really is truly remarkable, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "IGARO: It is amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Berry"]}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "It's a confirmation that, in fact, Amanda Berry has a child.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "You need police, fire or ambulance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I need police.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What's going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I've been kidnapped and I've been with him for ten years and I'm here, I'm free now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What's your address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I can't hear you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Hello?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Are they on their way right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "As soon as we get a car open.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Who's the guy you're -- who's the guy who went out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "His name is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "How old is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "He's like 52.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Is he white, black or Hispanic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "He's Hispanic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What's he wearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I don't know, because he's not here right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Who knows?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "The police are on the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Talk to them when they get there, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Tell me this, is there likely to be criticism of the police and the other investigators, that all of these girls have been found 10 years later, literally right under the noses of the investigators, a few blocks from where they disappeared?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Well, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["10 years later"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Is there any indication they were restrained where they were held?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "I can't go into any further specific details.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Can you comment on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "I can't go into any further specific details.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Did she feel any pain anywhere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Again, I'm sorry, I can't go into any further specific details.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Can you talk about their mental state?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Again, I can't really go into any further specific details.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Are family members with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Again, I can't go into any further specific details at the moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]